A Guide to the 1930-1999
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Alphabetical Files 1935-1994
  - O Nassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Osborn Letters, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Page 1933-1935 (Box 93)
  - Palmer, E. Holcombe 1991 (Box 93)
  - Patterson, Marc/4810 Grove Ave 1355-1485 1991 (Box 93)
  - Patton, Mrs. Frances Gray 1955-1958 (Box 93)
  - Paul, Eileen Susan, n.d. 1990-1991 (Box 93)
  - Payne, Fred 1959 (Box 93)
  - Peacock, Mr. Grant A., Sr. 1973, 1975-1987, 1990 (Box 93)
  - Peck, Scott 1987, 1989 (Box 93)
  - Peeples, Edward 1987 (Box 93)
  - Pennington, Buck, n.d. 1985-1987, 1992-1993 (Box 93)
  - Perkins, Drew 1993-1994 (Box 93)
  - Peterson, Virgilia (Mrs. Gouverneur Paulding), n.d. (Box 93)
  - Philips, Mr. and Mrs. Neil 1962 (Box 93)
  - Phillips, The Rev. Willie 1992 (Box 93)
  - Plaut, James S. and Mary, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Plummer, Jan E (Plummer, Jan E (Plummie) 1935 (Box 93)
  - Pollard, Chloe 1990 (Box 93)
  - Powell, Lewis and Jo, n.d. 1944, 1967, 1978-1980, 1982, 1986-1998 (Box 93)
  - Powers, Lee 1956, 1963, 1967, 1987-1990 (Box 93)
  - Preston, Alice 1961 (Box 93)
  - Princeton University Store 1964 (Box 93)
  - Price, Vincent 1964 (Box 93)
  - ?, Putsey 1934 (Box 93)
  - Quasha, Bill and Phyl 1967 (Box 93)
  - Rasmussen 1960 (Box 93)
  - Rathbone, Perry 1956 (Box 93)
  - Ready, Jackie 1990 (Box 93)
  - Redd, Mary M. ( Reddy), n.d. 1961, 1963 (Box 93)
  - Reed, Frederic Scott 1991 (Box 93)
  - Reed, Rossie and Billy 1965-1967 (Box 93)
  - Reniers, Perceval 1962 (Box 93)
  - Rhoads, Luci 1968 (Box 93)
  - Rice, Walter and Inger, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Roberts, Mr. and Mrs. George B 1967 (Box 93)
  - Robertson, Jaquelin Taylor 1986-1992 (Box 93)
  - Robb, Charles, n.d. 1982, 1988-1994 (Box 93)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette and John 1959-1966 (Box 93)
  - Rogers, Tweet Kimball 1962 (Box 93)
  - Room of one's own, n.d. 1964-1965, 1968 (Box 93)
  - Rose, David S. 1991 (Box 93)
  - Roosevelt, Kermit (Kim), n.d. (Box 93)
  - Rose, Kay and Chappie, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Rosenthal, Stephen (VA office of the Attorney General Information on DNA testing) 1989 (Box 93)
  - Rosenwald, Mr. and Mrs. Lessing Julius 1965 (Box 93)
  - Ross, Marvin and Lotus, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Rouse, James, n.d. 1981-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 93)
  - Roush, Dr. John 1993 (Box 93)
  - Rouse, Parke (Jr.), n.d. 1979-1987, 1983-1984, 1987-1988, 1990, 1992, 1994, 1997 (Box 93)
  - Rouse, Parke and Betsey 1968 (Box 93)
  - Roubin, Louis (Algonquin Books) 1986 (Box 93)
  - Ruddock, Mr. and Mrs. Albert 1957 (Box 93)
  - Ruddock, Merritt and Margaret 1962-1963 (Box 93)
  - Rust, Edwin C. 1983 (Box 93)
  - Ruzicka, Mr. Rudolph 1967 (Box 93)
  - Sachs, Dr. and Mrs Paul J., 1956-1957 (Box 93)
  - Saarinen, Eero and Aline 1961-1964 (Box 93)
  - Sands, Courtenay 1935 (Box 93)
  - Sampe, Astrio 1956 (Box 93)
  - Sanford, Helen Jewel 1993 (Box 93)
  - Scott, Mrs. George Cole 1967 (Box 93)
  - Scott, Mr. and Mrs. I.M. (Joanne) 1965 (Box 93)
  - Scott, Mildred, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Seward, Julie 1985 (Box 93)
  - Sedgwick, Paul 1966 (Box 93)
  - Sharpley, Philippa 1967 (Box 93)
  - Shirey, Francis M. (Box 93)
  - Sister Parrish 1995 (Box 93)
  - Sloane, Joseph Curtis (Box 93)
  - Smith, Dr. Beverly C./28 E. 73rd St., NYC, 10021 1985 (Box 93)
  - Speaker 1990 (Box 93)
  - Sprague, Rosemary, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Stettinius, Joseph 1988-1989 (Box 93)
  - Stevens, David H. and Mrs. (Ruth) 1956 (Box 93)
  - Stewart, Bob 1992, 1994 (Box 93)
  - Stewart, Henry Cary 1988 (Box 93)
  - Street, Levick 1934 (Box 93)
  - Sudler, Barbara, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Suggs, Dr. William Durwood and Grace, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Summer Party, n.d. 6/28/98, 1997-1998 (Box 93)
  - Switz, Don 1985-1986 (Box 93)
  - Tate, Darlene 1961 (Box 93)
  - Taylor, Herbert F 1992 (Box 93)
  - Taylor, Herbert 1991-1992 (Box 93)
  - Taylor, Peggy, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Taylor, Warrick 1963-1964, 1981 (Box 93)
  - Terry, Mary Sue, n.d. 1987-1994 (Box 93)
  - Terry, Quinlan 1989 (Box 93)
  - Thomas, Judge John Charles 1982 (Box 93)
  - Thomas, Virginia 1934 (Box 93)
  - Thompson, Ellen, n.d. 1988-1989 (Box 93)
  - Townsend, Mr. and Mrs. Lewis Raynham, (Anne) 1991 (Box 93)
  - Tree, Marietta, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Trevelleon, Jimmie 1961 (Box 93)
  - Tucker, Dr. H. St. George and Mary 1969-1970, 1992, 1996 (Box 93)
  - Tucker, Dr. and Mrs. W.E. ( Miss Molly) 1979 (Box 93)
  - Underwood, Mrs. Thomas (Frannie) 1965 (Box 93)
  - Valentine, Chamie 1991 (Box 93)
  - Van der Post, Sir Laurens 1988 (Box 93)
  - Vandiver, Dr. Frand E. 1984-1989 (Box 93)
  - Van Winkler, Julian P. Jr. 1963-1964 (Box 93)
  - Vernard W. Henley Gala 1991 (Box 93)
  - Vogt. Miss Antonie (Tonie) 1962-1963 (Box 93)
  - Walker, Sam and Beth 1968-1969 (Box 93)
  - Walker, John and Margaret 1954-1960, 1974 (Box 93)
  - Watkins, Hays T., n.d. 1992 (Box 93)
  - Watshon, Thomas John, Jr., 8 olive 1967-1969, 1991 (Box 93)
  - Warburg, Edward M.M. and Mary Whelan 1960 (Box 93)
  - Ware and Elise June 13, 1965 (Box 93)
  - Watlington, Mr. Hereward 1959 (Box 93)
  - Webb Party 30 July 1997 (Box 93)
  - Weedon May 11, 1968 (Box 93)
  - Weeks, Ted 1958-1982 (Box 93)
  - Whitehills 1951 (Box 93)
  - Whittle, The Rev. Dennis 1965 (Box 93)
  - Wicks, Edward 1966 (Box 93)
  - Wilder, L. Douglas, n.d. 1989-1994, 1998 (Box 93)
  - Wilkinson, J. Harvie, Jr., n.d. 1964, 1977, 1979-1980, 1990 (Box 93)
  - Williams, Dr. John Page, 1992 (Box 93)
  - Wilmington Friends June 12, 1965 (Box 93)
  - Wine Society 1989 (Box 93)
  - Williams, Langbourne 1958 (Box 93)
  - Wolff, Dr. and Mrs. Harold and Isabel Bishop, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Wood, Richard 1954-1974 (Box 93)
  - Wouk, Herman 1971 (Box 93)
  - Wyeth, Andrew and Betsy 1967 (Box 93)
  - Yelich, Nolan 1991 (Box 93)
  - Yerkes, David and Cath 1967 (Box 93)
  - Zapffe, Carl A. and Denise 1966 (Box 93)
  - Zehmer, David 1993 (Box 93)
  - Zuristein, Ann Freeman 1987 (Box 93)
  - Beginner's Guide to Bible Study, Grace and Holy Trinity October 1, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Bermuda Trip June 10-14, 1994 (Box 94)
  - Beyer, (Megan) Coffee 1997 (Box 94)
  - Birthday Cards, n.d. (Box 94)
  - William Byrd Community House, n.d. 1988-1989 (Box 94)
  - Charitable Contributions 1991-1992 (Box 94)
  - Charitable Contributions 1993 (Box 94)
  - Christmas 1991-1992 (Box 94)
  - Christmas Party 1991 (Box 94)
  - Christmas 1992 (Box 94)
  - Christmas 1993 (Box 94)
  - Circuit City Service 1995 (Box 94)
  - Conger, Clem, (Fine Arts Committee, Diplomatic Reception Rooms, U.S. Department of State) 1962-1964, 1992 (Box 94)
  - Dress Circle Party 22 September 1993 (Box 94)
  - Dress Circle-Cheek Medal 4 December 1994 (Box 94)
  - Enviroment 1989, 1991 (Box 94)
  - Freeman Chair, n.d. 1940, 1986-1990, 1992-1996 (Box 94)
  - Freeman Manuscript Project 1987-1990 (Box 94)
  - Friends of the Vassar Art Gallery, n.d. 1985 (Box 94)
  - Garden, n.d. 1991-1992 (Box 94)
  - Garden 1993 (Box 94)
  - Garden, n.d. 1995-1997 (Box 94)
  - Garden 1994 (Box 94)
  - The Last Review, V. Dabney 1980, 1984-1986 (Box 94)
  - The Last Parade 1983 (Box 94)
  - Lockgreen, n.d. (Box 94)
  - London, n.d. 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Magazine Subscriptions, n.d. 1969, 1971-1972, 1975-1977, 1979-1982, 1985, 1989-1991 (Box 94)
  - Miscellaneous-Personal 1994-1997 (Box 94)
  - A New Democracy, n.d. 1992 (Box 94)
  - Nutrition, n.d. 1977, 1986 (Box 94)
  - Organization 1982 (Box 94)
  - Piano Purchase 1992 (Box 94)
  - Prince Charles, Prince of Wales 1989-1990 (Box 94)
  - Richmonder of the Year 1990-1991 (Box 94)
  - Richmonder Times-Dispatch-Board of Contributors-Columns June 14, 1998, May 10, 1998, April 19, 1998, March 15, 1998, February 22, 1998 (Box 94)
  - Riverdance-(Mate and Sally) June 28th, 1997 (Box 94)
  - St. Catherine's School (Hair and Letter) 1934 (Box 94)
  - Standards Council Skit, n.d. (Box 94)
  - Rouse Dinner September 20, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Secretarial Expense 1987 (Box 94)
  - Secretarial Expense 1988 (Box 94)
  - Secretarial Expense 1989 (Box 94)
  - Secretarial Expense 1990 (Box 94)
  - Secretarial Expense 1991 (Box 94)
  - Secretarial Expense 1992 (Box 94)
  - Special Friends of MTMcC 1990 (Box 94)
  - Taxes 1985 (Box 94)
  - Taxes 1986 (Box 94)
  - Taxes 1987 (Box 94)
  - Taxes 1988 (Box 94)
  - Taxes 1989 (Box 94)
  - Taxes 1990 (Box 94)
  - Taxes 1991 (Box 94)
  - Taxes 1992 (Box 94)
  - Valentine's 1993 (Box 94)
  - Vassar College, n.d. 1991, 1993-1996 (Box 94)
  - Vassar College Commencement Program June 7, 1937 (Box 94)
  - Vassar Party November 29, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Verse, n.d. (Box 94)
  - Va. Interfaith Center for Public Policy, n.d. 1982-1984, 1987-1990 (Box 94)
  - Visitor Center Advisory Committee 1982, 1987-1988 (Box 94)
  - Volvo August 26, 1988 (Box 94)
  - Williamsburg February 1, 1989 (Box 94)
  - WXEX/TV 8, n.d. 1988 (Box 94)
  - Young People needing jobs 1982-1988 (Box 94)
  - YMCA Awards Luncheon 1986-1988 (Box 94)
  - Maymont AD HOC Committee 1986 (Box 95)
  - Maymont Benevolent Society, n.d. 1983-1987 (Box 95)
  - Maymont Benevolent Society, n.d. 1991-1995 (Box 95)
  - Maymont Floral Carriage Committee 1995 (Box 95)
  - Maymont Foundation, n.d. (1 of 2) 1988-1990 (Box 95)
  - Maymont Foundation, n.d. (2 of 2) 1988-1990 (Box 95)
  - Maymont Foundation 1995 (Box 95)
  - Maymont Foundation 1996 (Box 95)
  - Maymont Foundation 1997 (Box 95)
  - Maymont Historical Committee 1991-1997 (Box 95)
  - Maymont-Long Range Planning Committee, n.d. 1991-1992 (Box 95)
  - Maymont-Long Range Planning Committee 1996 (Box 95)
  - Maymont Nominating Committee 1995-1996 (Box 95)
  - RBHC-Annual Report 1991-1995 (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Appeals (Sample LISC), n.d. 1988-1989 (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Bunzl, Rudy and Esther, n.d. 1989, 1993 (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Cary Street 2000, n.d. 1992-1994 (Box 96)
  - Richmond Better Housing Coalition 1990 (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Executive Committee, n.d. 1994-1996 (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Finances 1989-1995 (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Ray Gindroz 1992-1993 (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Hope in the Cities, n.d. 1991-1997 (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Housing-Requests for Help 1991 (Box 96)
  - RBHC- I Have a Dream1989 (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Miscellaneous (1 of 2) (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Miscellaneous (2 of 2) (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Office Space VHDA-George Peterson, n.d. 1990-1991 (Box 96)
  - Photographs, n.d. (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Publications 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Publicity, n.d. 1988-1993 (Box 96)
  - Richmond First Club Housing Committee, n.d. 1987-1988 (Box 96)
  - Richmond Homebuilders Association 1989-1996 (Box 96)
  - Rouse, James W. (Enterprise Foundation), n.d. 1981, 1987-1991, 1996 (Box 96)
  - RBHC-Style Magazine Advertisements 1991 (Box 96)
  - T.C. Williams School of Law, n.d. 1988 (Box 96)
  - RBHC-(T.K. Somanath) To Dept. of Housing and Community Development Commonwealth of Virginia 7 July 1989 (Box 96)
  - RBHC-United Way, n.d. 1989-1991 (Box 96)
  - RR-Executive Committee, n.d. 1994-1995 (Box 96)
  - Search Committee 1989 (Box 96)
  - Stationary 1990 (Box 96)
  - Task Force on Community Outreach, UR 1990, 1992-1993 (Box 96)
  - VCDC-Correspondence Registration From Board 1996 (Box 96)
  - VHDA, n.d. 1988-1993 (Box 96)
  - Virginia Coalition for homeless, n.d. 1985-1994 (Box 96)
  - Virginia Museum 1992 (Box 96)
  - Va. Housing Partnership Fund Grant Repuest 1988, 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 96)
  - Wilder, Gov. Lawrence Douglas 1990 (Box 96)
  - Women and Housing Conference 1993-1995 (Box 96)
  - Work Plan 1991 (Box 96)
  - Young, Councilman Leonidas 1994 (Box 96)
  - Allen, Thomas N. (East Coast Oil) 1994 (Box 97)
  - Artze, Orlando, n.d. 1990-1994, 1996 (Box 97)
  - Atlanta 1991-1992 (Box 97)
  - Bank Account (RBHC) 1988 (Box 97)
  - Board Development Group-RBHC 1996 (Box 97)
  - Board of Directors RBHC, n.d. 1988-1995 (Box 97)
  - RBHC-Board of Directors, Meetings/Members List 1997-1998 (Box 97)
  - Board of Directors-Board List-RBHC, n.d. 1995-1998 (Box 97)
  - Board of Directors-Board List-RBHC, n.d. 1995-1998 (Box 97)
  - Building Better Communities 1993 (Box 97)
  - Carver Project, n.d. 1989, 1991 (Box 97)
  - Centralized Operations Committee 1991 (Box 97)
  - Chelsea Village, n.d. (Box 97)
  - Chespeake Corporation: Mr. Alvah H. Eubank Jr. 1989 (Box 97)
  - City Ventures, n.d. 1992 (Box 97)
  - Community Awareness and Public Policy-RBHC, n.d. 1988-1990 (Box 97)
  - Coordinating Committee, n.d. 1988 (Box 97)
  - Coordinator's Report 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 97)
  - Development Committee 1991 (Box 97)
  - Dominion Bank 1990 (Box 97)
  - East End Transformation Program 1992, 1994 (Box 97)
  - Editorial 6 Oct 1990 (Box 97)
  - Enterprise Corporation 1992-1993 (Box 97)
  - Episcopal Diocese of Virginia du Pont Grant 1994 (Box 97)
  - Executive Committee, n.d. 1996-1997 (Box 97)
  - Finance and Fund Raising Committee 1990-1991 (Box 97)
  - Finanace Task Force, n.d. 1987-1992 (Box 97)
  - Flood Wall 1990 (Box 97)
  - Forum on Homelessness (Richmond Area Forum on Homelessness) 1989 (Box 97)
  - Fund Development Committee, n.d. 1989-1990 (Box 97)
  - Virginia Council of Churches-Fund for Basic Human Needs 1989-1990 (Box 97)
  - RBHC Fundraising, n.d. 1985, 1991-1994 (Box 97)
  - Gifts-RBHC 1989 (Box 97)
  - Home 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 97)
  - Housing Development Support, n.d. 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 97)
  - Housing Start Program 1992 (Box 97)
  - Kemp, The Hon. Jack 1989 (Box 97)
  - Langston Terrace Housing Project (Rozanne Epps), n.d. (Box 97)
  - Legislative, n.d. 1988-1991 (Box 97)
  - LISC, Advisory Board, Current, n.d. 1997-1999 (Box 97)
  - LISC Advisory Committee, n.d. (1 of 2) 1991, 1995 (Box 97)
  - LISC Advisory Committee (2 of 2) 1995 (Box 97)
  - Lisc Advisory Committee 1995-1998 (Box 97)
  - LISC-Campaign Steering Committee, n.d. 1996 (Box 97)
  - LISC-Fundraising Lunch, n.d. 1994-1995 (Box 97)
  - LISC: Glazer/Ross, Carol, n.d. 1992, 1994, 1996 (Box 97)
  - LISC Search Committee 1996-1997 (Box 97)
  - Neighborhood Housing Development Task Force-RBHC, n.d. 1988-1989 (Box 97)
  - Neighborhood Services Survey, n.d. (Box 97)
  - Neighborhood Support Task Force-RBHC, n.d. 1988-1991 (Box 97)
  - Network News-Enterprise Foundation 1990 (Box 97)
  - Nominating Committee, n.d. 1992-1999 (Box 97)
  - Partnerships Newsletter 1988-1989 (Box 97)
  - RR-1988 Agenda 1987 (Box 98)
  - RR-Annual Meeting 1995 (Box 98)
  - RR-Citizen's Report 1991 (Box 98)
  - RR-City of Richmond Bank Participation Loan Program 1994 (Box 98)
  - RR-Crupi Report 1993 (Box 98)
  - RR-Cultural Link Trolley, n.d. 1987 (Box 98)
  - RR-Development Corporation, n.d. 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 98)
  - RR-Downtown Richmond, n.d. (Box 98)
  - RR-Economic Development Strategy, n.d. 1992-1993 (Box 98)
  - RR-EDAW-Hanna, H. Russell, Jr. 1989 (Box 98)
  - RR-Education Committee, n.d. 1992-1995 (Box 98)
  - RR-Executive Committee, n.d. 1995-1996 (Box 98)
  - RR-Financial Statements, Meeting 1993-1994, 1995 (Box 98)
  - RR-LDR International, n.d. 1990, 1992-1993 (Box 98)
  - RR-INTL. Downtown Association (39th Annual Conference) 1993 (Box 98)
  - RR-Merger (CRA and DRL-RR), n.d. 1996 (Box 98)
  - RR-Mission Statement and Program 1992-1993 (Box 98)
  - RR-Mission Statement and Proposed Program 1992-1993 (Box 98)
  - RR-News Clippings, n.d. (Box 98)
  - RR-News Clipping 1990 (Box 98)
  - RR-Newsletter?, 1989 (Box 98)
  - RR-Report on Examination of Financial Statements 1988 (Box 98)
  - RR-Retreat, City Council, n.d. (1 of 2) 1989-1991 (Box 98)
  - RR-Retreat, City Council (2 of 2) (Box 98)
  - RR-Retreat-Upper Brandon, n.d. 1992 (Box 98)
  - RR-Reynolds Metals Co., n.d. 1984-1985 (Box 98)
  - RR-Richmond Centre 1995 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Development Corp 1991-1994 (Box 98)
  - Riverfront Development Report, n.d. (Box 98)
  - RR-Riverfront Improvements Program, n.d. (1 of 2) 1984-1987 (Box 98)
  - RR-Riverfront Improvements Program, n.d. (2 of 2) 1988-1991 (Box 98)
  - RR-Statue Competition 1986 (Box 98)
  - RR-Strategic Plan 1995-1996 (Box 98)
  - RR-Townes, Clarence 1992-1993 (Box 98)
  - RR-Valentine Museum Proposal, n.d. 1987-1988, 1993 (Box 98)
  - RR-Virginia Research Park 1990 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum 1990-1991 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum 1994-1995 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum 9 October 1990 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum, December 1990 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum March 5, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum October 8, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum Dec. 10, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum March 3, 1992 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum, Correspondence, (Dr. Richmond Morrill) October 13, 1992 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum, Correspondence 8 December, 1992 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum 25, March, 1993 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum October 12, 1993 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum December 14, 1994 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum-Correspondence March 8, 1994 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum October 4, 1994 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum December 13, 1994 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum-Expenses 1991-1992 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum-Expenses 1992-1993 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum-Expenses 1993-1994 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum 1997-1998 (Box 98)
  - RUFF-HB 2604, n.d. 1997 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum-Membership 1990 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum Membership 1991-1992 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum Membership 1992 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum Membership 1993-1994 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum, Membership Survey, n.d. 1994 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum Planning Committee 1995-1996 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum Steering Committee, n.d. 1992-1993 (Box 98)
  - Richmond Urban Forum-Steering Committee 1991 (Box 98)
  - College of William and Mary 1993-1997 (Box 99)
  - Collegiate Schools 1992 (Box 99)
  - Douglas Southhall Freeman High School 1967, 1970, 1988-1996 (Box 99)
  - Henrico County Public Schools 1986-1987 (Box 99)
  - Hollins College, n.d. 1993-1997 (Box 99)
  - Hollins Overseers, n.d. 1991-1996 (Box 99)
  - The New Community School 1992-1994 (Box 99)
  - The New Community School 1994-1996 (Box 99)
  - St. Catherines School 1973-1993 (Box 99)
  - St. Catherines 1992 (Box 99)
  - St. Christopher's Endowment Campaign, n.d. 1981-1988 (Box 99)
  - Schools, n.d. 1986, 1989 (Box 99)
  - Steward School 1987, 1990 (Box 99)
  - University of Richmond 1994-1997 (Box 99)
  - U of R Board of Associates/Out Reach Task Force 1990 (Box 99)
  - UR, Jefferson School of Leadership Studies (Box 99)
  - UR, Jepson School 1994-1996 (Box 99)
  - UR, Jepson Evaluations 1994-1995 (Box 99)
  - UR-Virginia Cool, n.d. 1991-1992 (Box 99)
  - University of Richmond Service Associates 1996-1997 (Box 99)
  - University of Virginia 1996 (Box 99)
  - VCU 1994-1997 (Box 99)
  - Virginia Wesleyan College, Center for Study of Religious Freedom, n.d. 1996-1998 (Box 99)
  - Washington and Lee Oct. 20-21, 1995 (Box 99)
  - William and Mary 1977, 1980-1981, 1983-1986 (Box 99)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association America First Freedom (Box 100)
  - Proposed Interpretation for Stratford Hall-Robert E. Lee Memorial Association 1989 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Assoc, By-Laws Oct. 1990 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association Leadership in the American Revolution: Projects from the stratford Hall-Monticello Seminar for teachers 1988 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Foundation-Stratford Hall (History) 1968 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Hostesses Handbook, ca 1963 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Interpretation for Stratford Hall 1989 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Interpretation for Stratford Hall 1989 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Manual of Committees, April 1984 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Statford Hall Plantation, Manual of Handbooks 1972 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Minutes, April 26-30 1987 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Minutes, Oct 11-15 1987 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Minutes, April 24-28 1988 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Minutes, Oct 9-13 1988 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Minutes, April20-May 4 1989 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Minutes-October 8-12, 1989 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Minutes, April 28-May 2 1991 (Box 100)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Minutes, April 22-26 1990 (Box 101)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Minutes, October 12-18 1990 (Box 101)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Minutes, October 13-17 1991 (Box 101)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Minutes, October 18-22 1992 (Box 101)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Minutes, October 17-21 1993 (Box 101)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Inc, 63rd Spring Conference of Committees-Minutes, April 26-30 1992 (Box 101)
  - Sixty-Fourth Spring Conference of Committees of Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Inc. Minutes-April 25-29 1993 (Box 101)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Third Meeting of Lee Leadership Campaign Cabinet March 23, 1993 (Box Box 101)
  - Stratford Hall-Architectural Report by Phillips and Buchanan, v. 1, 1984 (Box 101)
  - Stratford Hall, Architectural Report by Phillips and Buchanan, v.2 1984 (Box 101)
  - Stratford Hall-Histories-including Title Search, n.d. (Box 101)
  - Stratford Hall (Maps, title research inventories, Accounts and Estate Records...etc) 1 of 2, n.d. (Box 101)
  - Stratford Hall (Map/title/structure/inventory) 2 of 2, n.d. (Box 101)
  - Stratford Hall-Newspaper Clippings, Notes, Correspondence-n.d. 1989 (Box 101)
  - Stratford Hall, Prime Travel Destination by Thomas G. McCaskey, Vice Presidential Colonial Williamsburg Foundation 1972 (Box 101)
  - Stratford Inventories, Synopsis, By Connie H Wyrick, n.d. (1758 and 1776) (Box 101)
  - St. Paul's Church, n.d. 1985-1986, 1989-1994 (Box 101)
  - St. Paul's Church 1988-1992 (Box 101)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal Church, n.d. 1993-1994 (Box 101)
  - St. Paul's AD HOC Committee, n.d. 1974, 1983-1994 (Box 101)
  - St. Pauls 150th Anniversary 1995-1996 (Box 101)
  - St. Pauls Church-Capital Fund Raising n.d. 1988-1991, 1995 (Box 101)
  - St. Paul's Church Endowment Fund Jan. 1993-Sept. 1996 (Box 101)
  - St. Paul's Church Endowment Fund, (1 of 2) 1997-1998 (Box 101)
  - St. Paul's Church Endowment Funds, Board of Management, (2 of 2) 1997-1998 (Box 101)
  - St. Paul's Housing Committee, n.d. 1990 (Box 101)
  - Undercroft-St. Paul's, n.d. 1984-1985 (Box 101)
  - Virginia Historical Society, n.d. 1983, 1985-1989 (Box 102)
  - Virginia Historical Society, n.d. 1984-1986, 1989 (Box 102)
  - Virginia Historical Society 1993-1997 (Box 102)
  - VHS, n.d., Sept. 1996 (Box 102)
  - Virginia Historical Society 1996-1997 (Box 102)
  - VHS-Board of Directors, (1 of 2) 1997 (Box 102)
  - VHS-Board of Directors (2 of 2) 1997 (Box 102)
  - Virginia Historical Society-Board of Trustees 1994 (Box 102)
  - Virginia Historical Society (Collections and Conservation Committee) 1993-1996 (Box 102)
  - VHS Committee Lists 1996-1997 (Box 102)
  - VHS-Publications and Education Committee 1993-1994 (Box 102)
  - Virginia Historical Society Symposium, May 5-6, n.d. 1989 (Box 102)
  - Virginia Historical Society (Trustees and Committees) 1994 (Box 102)
  - Washington and Lee 1994 (Box 102)
  - Webbers (UR) 1993 (Box 102)
  - VUU Pre School Conference 1992-1993 (Box 102)
  - Virginia Union University Academics Committee (1 of 2) 1986-1989 (Box 102)
  - Virginia Union University Academics Committee, n.d.(2 of 2) 1990-1993 (Box 102)
  - VUU Board 18-Nov., 1991 (Box 102)
  - VUU-Board of Trustees Meeting February 7, 1992 (Box 102)
  - VUU Board Meeting February 7, 1992 (Box 102)
  - Virginia Union Board Meeting May 1, 1992 (Box 102)
  - VUU Board Meeting November 6, 1992 (Box 102)
  - VUU Board Meeting February 5, 1993 (Box 102)
  - VUU Board of Trustees Meeting April 30, 1993 (Box 102)
  - VUU Board Meeting 5 Nov. 1993 (Box 102)
  - VUU Faculty Handbook of the College 15 Aug. 1992 (Box 102)